limelightbyalcone.com 2015-05-02

# Privacy | LimeLight by Alcone

We take our responsibility of protecting your personal information seriously and have created this Policy Statement to help you understand the type of information we collect and your rights to and our responsibilities in safeguarding it.

This Privacy Policy applies to any portion of the Alcone At Home website, including the official corporate website, Artists' personal websites and the Artist-only portion of the website, known as the “Green Room.” Alcone At Home respects the privacy of our Artists, customers and those who visit our websites and this Privacy Policy is incorporated into our Terms of Use. This online Privacy Policy does not necessarily cover or include the collection of personal information by an Alcone At Home Artist.

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, under certain conditions, disclose your personally identifiable information (“PII”) and the steps we have taken to secure your PII.

 **This Privacy Policy also explains your options regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your PII. This privacy policy applies to the Website and does not necessarily apply to any offline collection of your personal information.**

We do not require any PII to browse our Website. All information gathered is on a voluntary basis. If you decide to provide us with your PII, you should know that we may store all PII that you provide to us through whatever means you provide such information (through our Website, Artist, via email or facsimile, etc.). Examples of PII include but are not limited to, your name, physical and/or email address, phone number, and credit card information. In addition to your contact information, we may collect your personal tax id, birthday, gender, occupation, and any other information necessary for you to join us as an Artist.

## Cookies

We may collect non-personally identifiable information automatically through the use of “cookies.” Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive to collect information about your activities on our website. Cookies do not contain any PII unless you specifically supply that information. We use cookies to collect, store and sometimes tack information for statistical purposes to improve the services we provide. If you are a registered user, we will use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. Cookies also enable you to select products, place them in your shopping cart and to purchase the items. If you do this, we keep a record of your browsing activity and purchase. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your PII. You have the ability to set your browser to refuse cookies from websites or to remove cookies from your hard drive. If you choose to do this, you will not be able to access or use portions of the Website.

## Customer PII

To purchase Alcone At Home products, customers either fill out and sign an Oder Form at a Makeup Show or provide their information on-line via the Website. The PII provided on an Order Form will be entered into the Alcone At Home website by your Artist so we may process your order. All Artist must abide by this Privacy Policy and must not share confidential information except in connection with their Alcone At Home business, and they must make certain all Order Forms are kept in a secure location. Individuals interested in learning about being an artist or hostess will provide PII either on-line, via email or directly to an Alcone At Home Artist.

## Artist PII

To become an Alcone At Home Artist you must provide us with your PII through completing and digitally signing an on-line Artist Agreement.

## Age

We respect children's privacy. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information to us. You should rely on a parent or guardian to assist you.

## Internal Use

Alcone At Home will use the PII disclosed on an Order Form or entered into the Website to process and complete the customer's order, including shipping and billing. In addition, a customer's name, mailing address, email address and telephone number may be used for the following limited purposes:  
Referrals â€“ When Alcone At Home receives unsolicited orders or hostess requests, your PII will be provided to an artist to ensure your needs are met.â€¢ At Alcone At Home we want to ensure you are completely satisfied with your Alcone At Home purchase. Accordingly, the PII you provide may be used for purposes of monitoring and ensuring customer satisfaction, including troubleshooting problems and resolving disputes.â€¢ Your PII may also be used to keep you informed of new products and promotions at Alcone At Home.When a customer fills out and signs a Customer Order Form, they consent to the collection, use and disclosure of their PII for the purposes set out above, unless we are notified otherwise.

Alcone At Home may, from time to time, publish an Artist's PII (name, photo, sales results and achievements) to recognize the Artist for their achievements and help motivate other artists.

## Administrative

Alcone At Home reserves the right to use PII for administrative purposes. When an individual completes and digitally signs the New Artist Agreement, the individual consents to the collection, use and disclosure of their PII for the purposes set out above, including the calculation and processing of commissions, unless Alcone At Home is otherwise notified. When your Artist Application is accepted by Alcone At Home, the PII disclosed on the application, will be used solely within the context of our business relationship with you. Upon the termination of the relationship between Alcone At Home and the artist, Alcone At Home will only keep the artist's PII for lawful purposes.

## External Use

We want to provide you with excellent service and make your Alcone At Home experience as seamless as possible. We share nonpublic PII and non-personally identifiable information with third parties that perform services on our behalf for your benefit. These third parties must abide by this Policy to keep nonpublic information confidential and use it only for its intended purpose. You acknowledge that Alcone At Home is located in the United States and, accordingly, your information may be processed and stored in the United States and that the US government, courts or law enforcement agencies may be able to obtain disclosure of your information through lawful means in the US. We may also disclose PII for detection and prevention of fraud. We reserve the right to transfer PII in the event Alcone At Home acquires or merges with or is acquired by another company. Any information disclosed as a result of one of these events will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time.

## External Use

We do not rent or sell your PII to another company or third party business for use in promoting their goods or services.

## Opt In

Alcone At Home Main Office will only provide you with promotional emails, coupons, etc if you opt-in to receive these emails. You may, however, receive emails of varying content directly from your Artist.

## Security

To protect your nonpublic PII, we have put in place state-of-the-art sockets layer (SSL) technology. Please note that email is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting credit card numbers or other sensitive information. Alcone At Home will NEVER ask for sensitive information via email.

## Choice

You may review, correct, or delete your personal information through our website. If you have registered with us, you will be able to view and modify any information contained in your personal profile. However, for security purposes, you must contact Alcone At Home directly to change your tax id number. You may also contact us to remove any PII from our database.
